Marilyn: And now for…something old, something new, something borrowed, and something blue.
Susan: OK. Let’s see. Something borrowed. That’s this dress. Borrowed from Marilyn.
Ellen: Something blue. My wristband. I wore it when I married your father.
Susan: Oh, Mother. I forgot you still had it. It’s just so lovely.
Ellen: I bought it in an antique shop when I was about eighteen years old. I saved it for my wedding day.
Susan: And you saved it for me, didn’t you, Mother?
Ellen: Yes, honey I did. Are we ever going to finish?
Ellen: All right. OK. Something borrowed.
Marilyn: The wedding dress. And something blue.
Susan: The wristband. Something old?
Ellen: Something old. Right. What’s old?
Susan: Of course! Something old. I had planned to wear them.
Ellen: Grandma’s pearls! Oh, Grandpa will be so pleased that you’re wearing them. I’m sure he misses Grandma on a day like this.
Susan: Help me with them, Marilyn. I’ve never worn them before. I’ve been saving them for today.
Ellen: Saving them for today? Oh, you’re a real Stewart!
Marilyn: Oh, there you go. Lovely!
Ellen: Lovely!
Susan: Lovely!
Marilyn: Something borrowed, something blue. Something old… and now for something new.
Susan: The veil. Oh, it’s so beautiful, Marilyn!
Ellen: You really are a fabulous designer, Marilyn.
Marilyn: Doesn’t it look just right on Susan?
Ellen: Perfect!
Marilyn: And when you both say, “I do,” Harry will lift this veil over your head and kiss the bride.
Ellen: Oh, I’m so excited!
Susan: When you said, “I do, ” Marilyn, it suddenly became real.
Marilyn: That’s all right, Susan. You’ve got the wedding-day jitters! In less than two hours, you will be Mrs. Harry Bennett.
Ellen: Oh, that reminds me. If we don’t get dressed, we won’t be there to see Susan become Mrs. Harry Bennett.
Susan: Before you leave-do I look all right?
Ellen: You never looked better.
Susan: Mom.
Marilyn: She’s right. And that’s dear little Max. Got to go and feed him.
Susan: What am I Supposed to do?
Marilyn: Take off the veil, kick off your shoes, and sit down.
Ellen: We’ll come upstairs and get you in a little while.
Marilyn: Richard’s going to take some wedding pictures before the ceremony. So just relax.
Susan: Are you kidding? Relax?
Susan: Susan Stewart…you are about to become Susan Bennett-Mrs. Harry Bennett.